<exhibit-encounter-cards type="the curse of the dark pharoah">
    <!-- Cult Encounter 1 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>A Chance Encounter</title>
        <entry>
            A stranger with a large canvas sack sees you in the crowd and begins to quickly run the other direction. You may make a Speed (-2) check to try to catch him. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, you are delayed while you search fruitlessly for him 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the French Hill Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 2 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>A Corrupting Influence</title>
        <entry>
            Someone close to you has been corrupted by the Pharaoh's dark power. You must either return one of your Ally cards to the box or raise the terror level by one. Then gain an Exhibit Item. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Downtown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 3 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>An Inside Job</title>
        <entry>
            A museum guard has taken a relic, hoping that you can use it to serve a greater purpose. You may make a Lore (-2) check to prove you can. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Easttown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 4 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>An Insidious Trap</title>
        <entry>
            A plain, unmarked crate sits on the sidewalk. If you choose to open it, gain 2 Exhibit Items, and a gate and a monster appear. If you choose not to open it, nothing happens. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Miskatonic University Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 5 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>An Intruder in the Mind</title>
        <entry>
            You discover a man in a deep trance-like state clutching an artifact. Do you dare touch the object? You may make a Will (-2) check. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, lose 3 Clue tokens. If you have less than 3 Clue tokens, lose all of them. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Downtown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 6 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Ancient Artifact on Display</title>
        <entry>
                The museum staff has brought one of the artifacts to this part of town to attract more visitors. You may make a Sneak (-2) check. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, you are arrested. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Uptown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 7 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Carnivorous Beetles</title>
        <entry>
            You discover a body covered with swarming insects. The corpse is clutching a relic from the exhibit in its hands. You may make a Will (-2) check. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, raise the terror level by one.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Southside Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 8 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Hidden in Plain Sight</title>
        <entry>
            A street vendor is selling cheap copies of items on display at the museum, but one of the objects he has for sale seems to be the genuine article. You may spend $3 to make a Luck (-2) check. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the French Hill Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 9 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>It Calls from Beyond</title>
        <entry>
            It's here, you can feel it in your bones. But where? You may make a Luck (-2) check to search every possible hiding place. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, lose 1 Sanity in frustration.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Miskatonic University Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 10 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>It Keeps a Constant Vigil</title>
        <entry>
            A monster appears! If you defeat the monster, gain an Exhibit Item. If you are knocked unconscious or driven insane by the monster, add a doom token to the doom track. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Rivertown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 11 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Lost in Transit</title>
        <entry>
            A driver is examining a number of unlabeled boxes in his truck and would be glad to have help identifying them. Make a Lore (-2) check. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, you are delayed. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Southside Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 12 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Purified by Fire</title>
        <entry>
            A woman is dousing an artifact from the exhibit in gasoline. Make a Speed (-2) check to stop her from burning the object. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Northside Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 13 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Quid Pro Quo</title>
        <entry>
            A wild-eyed man says he found a trinket outside the museum and is willing to trade. You must discard any combination of 2 Common or Unique Items and draw 1 Exhibit Item. If you are unable to discard the items, he curses you instead.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Rivertown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 14 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Stolen Property for Sale</title>
        <entry>
            Arkham's criminals are offering stolen museum property, and they wont take no for an answer. You must pay $4 and draw one Exhibit Item. If you are unable to pay, you lose 1 Stamina instead.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Uptown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 15 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>The Application of Force</title>
        <entry>
            You find a metal box with a large lock. Make a Fight (-2) check to smash the lock open. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box, as the box and its contents are irreparably damaged.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Merchant District Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 16 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>The Culprit Apprehended</title>
        <entry>
            Sheriff Engle has caught a thief, but has not yet found the loot! you may make a Sneak (-2) check to covertly find it first. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Easttown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 17 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>The Legacy of Anubis</title>
        <entry>
            A pack of dogs surround a crate labeled as property of the museum. You may make a Fight (-2) check to fend them off. If you pass, gain an Exhibit Item. If you fail, lose 1 Stamina.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Merchant District Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 18 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Too Late</title>
        <entry>
            There's an acrid smell here and a few drops of blood, but nothing else. The artifact from the exhibit is gone. Take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Northside Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
</exhibit-encounter-cards>
