<exhibit-encounter-cards type="miskatonic horror">
    <!-- Cult Encounter 1 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>A Curse on Thieves</title>
        <entry>
            Someone has written hieroglyphics on the wall, warning of a curse upon those who disturb the Pharoah&apos;s tomb. If you are currently Cursed, make a Luck (+0) check. If you fail, you are devoured.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Uptown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 2 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>A Handful of Ashes</title>
        <entry>
            You grab the artifact you&apos;d been seeking, but it collapses into dust and your mind suddenly opens to the thoughts of those around you. Take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box. Then take the Psychic card if it is available.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Miskatonic University Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 3 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>It Has Infected Your Soul</title>
        <entry>
            The rumors were true; you find one of the objects intended for the museum. But once you place your hands on it you can feel its evil sinking into you. Gain an Exhibit Item and then take the Tainted card if it is available.
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Northside Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 4 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Its Power Still Lingers</title>
        <entry>
            The museum&apos;s treasure was destroyed, but while touching the pieces that remain, your mind is taken to events that have yet to occur. Take the top card from the Exhibit Item deck and return it to the box. Then take the Visions card if it is available. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Easttown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 5 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Purge the Unclean</title>
        <entry>
            Father Michael has already searched this neighborhood. He tells you he needs someone to help him destroy these abominable relics. If you do not currently have an Exhibit Item, take the Anointed card if it is available. Otherwise, nothing happens. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Downtown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 6 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Someone Has to Take the Fall</title>
        <entry>
            The ancient object was right where you were told it would be. And now you're right where you need to be for the police to blame you for the museum's robbery. Gain an Exhibit Item and then take the Wanted card if it is available. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the French Hill Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 7 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>They Will Never Let You Rest</title>
        <entry>
            A badly injured man clutches one of the Ancient Egyptian artifacts. He uses the last of his strength to give the object to you and warn you that the evil forces will pursue this item relentlessly. Gain an Exhibit Item and then take the Harried card if it is available. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Southside Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 8 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>This Was a Set Up</title>
        <entry>
            You were lured here by a private investigator working for the museum. If you're on the level, he may help you. If you do not currently have an Exhibit Item, take the Private Investigator card if it is available. Otherwise, nothing happens. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Rivertown Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
    <!-- Cult Encounter 9 -->
    <exhibit-encounter>
        <title>Travelers in Need of Help</title>
        <entry>
            A group of museum curators from Cairo are having a hard time navigating Arkham. They seek your help getting one last artifact to Arkham's museum. Gain an Exhibit Item and then take the Local Guide card if it is available. 
        </entry>
        <location>
            Move the Ancient Whispers marker to the Merchant District Street Location.
        </location>
    </exhibit-encounter>
</exhibit-encounter-cards>
