<?xml version="1.0" ?><reckoning-cards expansion_set="the lurker at the threshold"><reckoning><title>A Humble Servant</title><entry>Add 1 doom token to the doom track for each investigator with 3 Dark Pacts.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>A Little Taste</title><entry>The investigator(s) with the least Power gain 1 Power, even if he does not have a Dark Pact. Note, however, that an investigator needs a Dark Pact to spend Power.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>An Offer You Can&apos;t Refuse</title><entry>The first player chooses an investigator. That investigator must take a Dark Pact if able. If not able, that investigator is devoured.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Bargain of the Gate</title><entry>The investigator with the most Power moves to the Other World of his choice (ties broken by the first player).</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Dark Reward</title><entry>Each investigator with a Dark Pact gains 1 Power per Dark Pact he has.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Debt Comes Due</title><entry>For each 3 Power possessed by the investigators as a group, add 1 doom token to the doom track (round down).</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Devil&apos; Bargain</title><entry>The investigators must choose: either each investigator with Power must discard a Common or Unique Item, or add 1 doom token to the doom track.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Further Temptation</title><entry>Each investigator with a Dark Pact draws 1 Spell.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Give the Devil his Due</title><entry>Each investigator with a Dark Pact must discard 1 Gate trophy or 5 toughness worth of monster trophies or 5 Clue tokens, if able. If he cannot, he must discard all his monster trophies and Clues.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>He Is Everywhere</title><entry>If every investigator has 1 or more Dark Pacts and/or 1 or more Power, add a doom token to the doom track.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Humanity Lost</title><entry>The investigator with the most Power is devoured (ties broken by the first player). If no investigators have Power, there is no effect.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>In Too Deep</title><entry>Each investigator with only 1 Dark Pact must immediately choose and take a second Dark Pact.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Power Begets Power</title><entry>Each investigator with at least 1 Power gains 1 Power.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Power Corrodes</title><entry>Each investigator loses 1 Sanity for each Power he has.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Power Corrupts</title><entry>Each investigator loses 1 Sanity or 1 Stamina for each Power he has.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Power Decays</title><entry>Each investigator loses 1 Stamina for each Power he has.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Prisoner&apos;s Dilemma</title><entry>The investigators must choose: either the investigator with the most Power is devoured, or the investigator with the least Power is driven insane.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Spread the Word</title><entry>Each investigator may choose to gain one or more Dark Pacts. Then, if there is at least one investigator who does not have a Dark Pact, each investigator who does have a Dark Pact is Cursed.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Strange Behavior</title><entry>Each investigator with a Bound Ally must discard 3 Clue tokens. For each investigator that fails to do this, increase the terror level by 1.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Terrible Realization</title><entry>Each investigator with a Blood Pact loses 2 Sanity.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>The Body a Temple</title><entry>Each investigator with a Soul Pact loses 2 Stamina.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>The Body Decays</title><entry>Each investigator with a Dark Pact loses 1 Stamina per Dark Pact he has.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>The Master of Magic</title><entry>Each investigator with at least 1 Spell gains 1 Power.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>The Mind Unravels</title><entry>Each investigator with a Dark Pact loses 1 Sanity per Dark Pact he has.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Through the Threshold</title><entry>Every investigator in Arkham with 1 or more Power is drawn through the closest open Gate (his choice if there is a tie).</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Turning On One Another</title><entry>Discard 1 Ally from the Ally deck for each Bound Ally card in play. For each Ally that you cannot discard (because the deck is empty), increase the terror level by 1.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Uncertain Future</title><entry>Shuffle the Reckoning deck and its discard pile together (including this card), then draw a new Reckoning card.</entry></reckoning><reckoning><title>Unsettling Aura</title><entry>If the total Power possessed by the investigators as a group is greater than the total number of investigators in the game, increase the terror level by 1.</entry></reckoning></reckoning-cards>